Finding Aid for Edward M. Honey photographs, 1903-1929
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Edward M. Honey photographs 1903-1929
Honey, Edward M.
0.3 linear feet
92272 Aa 2
Detroit, Michigan, resident; Detroit area construction photographs.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was donated by Kay Schwartz (donor no. 5859 ).
No further additions to the collection are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Edward M. Honey was resident of Detroit, Michigan.
The collection consists of construction photographs of buildings in Detroit, Michigan in the period of 1903 to 1929. The collection also includes two albums, in one of which there are photographs of Hill Auditorium in Ann Arbor in 1912.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Buildings--Michigan--Detroit.; Construction industry.; Detroit (Mich.); Detroit (Mich.)--Buildings.; Hill Auditorium (University of Michigan); Laborers.
Genre Terms:
Cyanotypes.; Photographs.
- Photographs
  - Barlum Tower, Detroit, 1927 (Box 1)
    (folder no. 1)
  - Bell Telephone Building, Detroit, 1927 (Box 1)
    (folder no. 2)
  - Fort Shelby Hotel, Detroit, 1927 (Box 1)
    (folder no. 3)
  - Hunter Building, Detroit, 1911 (Box 1)
    (folder no. 4)
  - Michigan State Fair, 1929 (Box 1)
    (folder no. 5)
  - Miscellaneous, Detroit
    (folder no. 6)
    - Palms Building, 1908 (Box 1)
    - 1200 Washington Boulevard (Box 1)
    - Vocational High School (Box 1)
    - Masonic Temple (Box 1)
  - Unidentified, 1911 (Box 1)
    (folder no. 7)
  - Unidentified, 1914-1920 (Box 1)
    (folder no. 8)
  - Unidentified, 1922 (Box 1)
    (folder no. 9)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 1)
    (folder no. 10)
- Albums
  - Album, 1911; include Hunter Building, Detroit and unidentified building next to Detroiter Abend Post Building (Box 1)
  - Album, 1903-1912 (Box 1)
    (include Hill Auditorium, Ann Arbor, 1912, Palms Building, 1908, unidentified building, 1903, next to State Savings Bank, Detroit; Wayne Pavilion, 1908, and Y.M.C.A., Detroit, 1908)